Jonathan Grangien

CV/resume

EXPERIENCE

Sept 2016 - Present

Studentfiket Webmaster

As webmaster of the student driven café and organization Studentfiket, I maintain administration and uptime of the current website. I am also developing a new React-Redux-Node application from scratch to replace said website, which is proving to be my most exciting web project so far.

Sept 2015 - Sept 2016

Media Technology Days

Webmaster

Took part in planning and work behind the exhibit event The Media Technology Days, which aims to inspire and connect students and business. As webmaster I was responsible for managing the Rubyon-Rails webapp medieteknikdagarna.se and things web related.

Sept 2015 - Present

LiTHehack

Programming Tutor

Taking part in the student-driven organization LiTHehack at Linköping University, I help peers with programming related labs, projects or questions.

Some Public Projects

2016 **TowerVR**

(youtube.com/watch?v=2eBE4bzM2sw)

Multiplayer VR game for the Google Cardboard. The game is tech-focused, achieving to implement rendered avatars of other players through posi-

tion tracking.

2016 **SPH Fluid Sim**

(youtube.com/watch?v=cd76KeGxVsc) Real time interactive 3D water simulation on the GPU based on the Navier-Stokes equations. Implements OpenCL and a GUI for changing physical con-

stants during run-time.

2015

(jonathangrangien.se/myGalaxy)

An interactive WebGL application I worked on in a team of five during a comp. graphics course. A user can create planets and customize it among those created by others.

Källvindsgatan 23 A 60240 - Norrköping, Sweden

+46 73 365 1112 7

jonathan.grangien@gmail.com \bowtie

www.jonathangrangien.se

SUMMARY

Student of the M.Sc Computer Science in Media Technology engineering programme at Linköping University, Sweden. The courses I have taken at the university - many of which group project oriented - have given me solid grounds in tech, and I have gained experience through several engagements alongside studies. My main skill is web development, but I am enthusiastic about computer graphics.

EDUCATION

2013 - 2018MSc comp. sc.

Mediatechnology

Linköpings Universitet,

Norrköping

2009 - 2012 **Natural Science Program**

High School

NT Gymnasiet, Stockholm

COMMUNICATION SKILLS

SWEDISH Native

ENGLISH Oral: Proficient, written: Native

Oral: Good JAPANESE

Oral: Basic, written: Good FRENCH

SOFTWARE SKILL LEVELS

C++, JavaScript (es6, React),

HTML/CSS, git, Unix, Vim

Intermediate Java, Matlab, PHP, LTFX,

MySQL

BASIC Python, Windows, Postgres,

MongoDB